International Programs, Campus Coordinator Records 1971-1984
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Assistant to the Director of Resident Instruction (Campus Coordinator), 2
  - University of Jordan, Assistantships, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 221)
    - Jordanian Students, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 299)
      - Nazir Hadidi, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 307)
      - Butras Hattar, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 308)
      - Muhammod Shatanawi, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 309)
      - Abram Steitieh, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 310)
      - Muhammad Suwwan, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 311)
      - Mostafa Qrunfleh, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 312)
      - Special Costs, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 313)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Air Freight, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 314)
      - Insurance under AID Contract, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 315)
      - Jordan Visit, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 316)
      - Meeting Notes, Dean of Agriculture, Trip to Jordan, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 317)
      - Farhan-Qasem Visit to WSU, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 318)
      - Overseas Mail, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 319)
      - Per Diem Rates, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 320)
      - Travel, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 321)
      - Trip to Jordan, 1976-1979 (Box 27, Folder 322)
      - Trip to Jordan, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 323)
      - Visa Requirements, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 324)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 325)
    - Personnel, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 326)
    - Personnel, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 327)
    - Personnel, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 328)
      - Chief of Party, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 329)
      - Sample Letter, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 330)
      - Day Bassett, Final Report, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 331)
      - Harry Cosgriffe, 1975-1978 (Box 28, Folder 332)
      - P.C. Crandall, Final Report, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 333)
      - I. A. Dyer, 1975-1979 (Box 28, Folder 334)
      - Yoshio Ehara, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 335)
      - Brooks Hanford, 1975-1979 (Box 28, Folder 336)
      - Max Jensen, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 337)
      - Max Jensen, 1977-1978 (Box 28, Folder 338)
      - Fenton Larsen, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 339)
      - June Roberts, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 340)
      - Gaylord Mink, Research Report, 1976-1978 (Box 28, Folder 341)
      - Lowell Rasmussen, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 342)
      - J. F. Schafer, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 343)
      - C. Gardner Shaw, 1977-1980 (Box 29, Folder 344)
      - C. Gardner Shaw, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 345)
        - Final Report, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 346)
        - Travel, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 347)
      - Esther Anne Shaw, Travel, 1977-1979 (Box 29, Folder 348)
      - P.C. Thompson, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 349)
      - Perry Triplett, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 350)
      - Robert Wilcox, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 351)
      - Robert Wilcox, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 352)
    - Project Continuation, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 353)
    - Project Director
      - General Information, Travel, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 354)
      - Copy of JORDAN TIMES 1976, JORDAN, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 355)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 356)
    - Purchasing Office, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 357)
    - Purchasing Office, Requisition Forms, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 358)
    - Purchasing Office, Memorandum, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 359)
    - Purchase Orders
      - 1975 (Box 30, Folder 360)
      - 1975 (Box 30, Folder 361)
      - 1975, 1976, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 362)
      - 1975 (Box 30, Folder 363)
      - 1976 (Box 30, Folder 364)
      - 1976 (Box 30, Folder 365)
      - 1976 (Box 30, Folder 366)
      - 1976 (Box 30, Folder 367)
      - 1976 (Box 30, Folder 368)
      - 1976 (Box 30, Folder 369)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 370)
      - 1977 (Box 31, Folder 371)
      - 1977 (Box 31, Folder 372)
      - 1977 (Box 31, Folder 373)
      - 1977 (Box 31, Folder 374)
      - 1977 (Box 31, Folder 375)
      - 1978 (Box 31, Folder 376)
      - 1978 (Box 31, Folder 377)
      - 1979 (Box 31, Folder 378)
      - 1979 (Box 31, Folder 379)
      - 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 380)
    - Reports, Final
      - Max Jensen, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 381)
      - Fenton Larsen, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 382)
      - Lowell Rasmussen, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 383)
      - C. Gardner Shaw, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 384)
      - Robert Wilcox, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 385)
    - Reports, Quarterly, 1976-1978 (Box 32, Folder 386)
    - Reports, Quarterly, 1976-1979 (Box 32, Folder 387)